Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins MC.286
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection of Course Bulletins
1832-ongoing
New York University Archives
New York University
MC.286
130 Linear Feet in 378 bound volumes and 198 boxes
244.6 Megabytes in 46 computer files
392 websites in 392 archived websites.
The collection consists of publications (bulletins, catalogs, announcements, etc.) that outline the course of study at New York University and its component schools, dating from 1832 to the present day. The publications are a mix of bound and unbound materials, as well as electronic records in pdf and .doc format and websites containing details about course offerings at NYU. They typically include an overview of the school, degree requirements, lists of faculty and administrators, and course descriptions. Early publications sometimes include lists of students and degrees conferred.
Conditions Governing Access
Material pertaining to individual student records may be restricted in accordance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Please contact the Archives with specific questions regarding access to such records.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; provenance is unknown. Material from 2020 accretion was donated by Richard Carreno in July 2019. The accession number associated with this donation is 2020.003.
Prior to 2018, websites were initially selected by curators and captured through the use of the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2019, accessioning information for archived websites were recorded. Websites were added either due to content drift, link rot, or were selected by the University Archivist. The accession numbers associated with these websites are 2019.090, 2019.091, 2019.092, 2019.098, 2019.099, 2019.100, 2019.101, 2019.102, 2019.103, 2019.104, 2019.105, 2019.117, 2019.127, 2019.129, 2019.132, 2020.003, 2020.010, 2020.022, 2020.024, 2020. 026, 2020.028, 2020.031, 2021.010, 2021.013, 2021.018, 2021.023, 2021.024, 2021.025, 2021.026, 2021.027, 2021.028, 2021.029, 2021.030, 2021.031, 2021.032, 2021.034, 2021.035. 2022 archived website accessions are 2022.013, 2022.015, 2022.016, 2022.017, 2022.055, 2022.089, and 2022.090. 2023 archived website accessions are 2023.013, 2023.031, 2023.054, and 2023.056. 2024 archived website accessions are 2024.017, 2024.026, 2024.061, 2024.062, and 2024.074.
An accretion of downloaded pdf and .doc files was accessioned in April 2022 as 2022.019.
Existence and Location of Copies
Additional duplicate copies of publications are held in the collection of New York University Publications (preservation copies) (RG 1.0). Digitized course bulletins and catalogues are available on Hathi Trust, https://catalog.hathitrust.org/Record/005398978 and https://catalog.hathitrust.org/Record/005412102.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into series based on the New York University Archives's record group classification system, then by date. Titles for the record groups are based on the school or program's current official name (as of 2019). For example, School of Commerce bulletins are included as part of the Stern School of Business record group.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of publications (bulletins, catalogs, announcements, etc.) that outline the course of study at New York University and its component schools, dating from 1832 to the present day. The publications are a mix of bound and unbound materials, as well as electronic records in pdf and .doc format and websites containing details about course offerings at NYU. They typically include an overview of the school, degree requirements, lists of faculty and administrators, and course descriptions. Early publications sometimes include lists of students and degrees conferred.
Education, Higher.; Universities and Colleges -- Curricula.; Bulletins.
- All University (RG 1), 1832-1978, 2015-ongoing
  - Election of Officers of the University of the City of New York, Preparatory Studies, and Course of Study, 1832; cuid18154 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Excerpts from Minutes of the Faculty of the University of the City of New York, 1832; cuid18197 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - University of the City of New-York, 1835; cuid18198 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - University of the City of New-York, 1836; cuid18199 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Announcement and Schedule of University of the City of New-York Classes, 1836; cuid18200 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Announcement and Schedule of University of the City of New-York Classes, 1837; cuid18201 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Catalogue of the Officers, Alumni, and Students, of the University of the City of New-York, 1839-1840; cuid18202 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Catalogue of the Officers, Alumni, and Students, of the University of the City of New-York, 1840-1841; cuid18203 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Catalogue of the Officers, Alumni, and Students, of the University of the City of New-York, 1841-1842; cuid18204 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Catalogue of the Officers, Alumni, and Students, of the University of the City of New-York, 1842-1843; cuid18205 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of the University of the City of New-York, 1843-1844; cuid18206 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of the University of the City of New York, 1844-1845; cuid18207 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of the University of the City of New York, 1845-1846; cuid18208 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of the University of the City of New York, 1846-1847; cuid18209 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of the University of the City of New York, 1847-1848; cuid18210 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of the University of the City of New York, 1848-1849; cuid18211 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of the University of the City of New York, 1849-1850; cuid18212 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Circular of the Faculty of Science and Letters of the University of the City of New York, June 1851; cuid18213 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Alumni of the University of the City of New York, 1852; cuid18214 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Circular of the Faculty of Science and Letters of the University of the City of New York, July 1852; cuid18215 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students and Register of Societies in the University of the City of New-York, 1852-1853; cuid18216 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Circular of the Faculty of Science and Letters of the University of the City of New York (Revised), February 1853; cuid18266 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Circular of the University of the City of New-York, June 1854; cuid18217 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - University of New-York Medical Department, Annual Announcement of Lectures with Catalogues of Students and Graduates, 1855-1856; cuid18155 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Circular and Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, March 1856; cuid18218 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New-York, March 1857; cuid18219 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, March 1858; cuid18220 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, March 1859; cuid18221 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, March 1860; cuid18222 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, 1860-1861; cuid18223 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Catalogues of the University of the City of New York, Volume II, 1861-1875; cuid18196 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, 1861-1862; cuid18224 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, 1862-1863; cuid18225 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, 1863-1864; cuid18226 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - A General Catalogue of the University of the City of New-York, 1864; cuid18236 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New-York, March 1864; cuid18227 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, March 1865; cuid18267 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - University of the City of New-York, 1867; cuid18228 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New-York, March 1869; cuid18268 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New-York, March 1870; cuid18229 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Circular of the University of the City of New-York, August 1871; cuid18230 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, 1873-1874; cuid18231 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New-York, 1874-1875; cuid18232 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New-York, 1875-1876; cuid18233 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New-York, 1876-1877; cuid18234 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, 1877-1878; cuid18235 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Catalogues of the University of the City of New York, 1877-1881; cuid18269 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, 1878-1879; cuid18237 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, 1879-1880; cuid18238 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Catalogues, 1881-1888 (Box 3)
  - A General Catalogue of the University of the City of New York, Departments of Arts and Science, 1882; cuid18156 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1885-1886; cuid18157 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1886-1887; cuid18158 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Catalogues, 1888-1892 (Box 4)
  - Catalogues, 1892-1894, 1913-1917 (Box 5)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes Department of English (1914-1915) and Modern Language Group (1916-1917)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1887-1888; cuid18159 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1888-1889; cuid18160 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1889-1890; cuid18161 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1890-1891; cuid18162 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1891-1892; cuid18163 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1892-1893; cuid18164 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1893-1894; cuid18165 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - The University of the City of New York Catalogue and Announcements, 1894-1895; cuid18166 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - New York University Catalogue and Announcements, 1895-1896; cuid18167 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - New York University Catalogue, 1896-1897; cuid18168 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - New York University Catalogue and Announcements, 1897-1898; cuid18169 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - New York University Catalogue and Announcements, 1898-1899; cuid18170 (Box 218, Folder 4, Box 219, Folder 1)
  - New York University Catalogue and Announcements, 1899-1900; cuid18171 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Announcements and Sixty-Eighth Commencement Program, 1900-1901 (Box 196)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1900-1901 (Box 196)
  - Bi-Weekly Bulletin (Vol I. No. 1), February 1901 (Box 178)
  - Bi-Weekly Bulletins (Bound Volumes I-IV), 1901-1905 (Box 193)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1901-1902 (Box 196)
  - General University Catalogue (Vol. II No. 2), February 1902 (Box 178)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1902-1903 (Box 196)
  - Bi-Weekly Bulletin (Vol. IV No. 1), January 1903 (Box 178)
  - General University Catalogue (Vol. III No. 1), January 1903 (Box 178)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1903-1904 (Box 196)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1904-1905 (Box 196)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1905-1906 (Box 196)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1906-1907 (Box 197)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1907-1908 (Box 197)
  - Catalogue and Announcements, 1908-1909 (Box 197)
  - Catalogue, 1909-1910 (Box 197)
  - Catalogue, 1910-1911 (Box 197)
  - Catalogue, 1911-1912 (Box 197)
  - Catalogue, 1912-1913 (Box 198)
  - Catalogue, 1913-1914 (Box 198)
  - Announcements - Summer School and Courses Abroad, 1914 (Box 198)
    Includes announcements for study abroad programs and an assortment of other courses.
  - Catalogue, 1914-1915 (Box 198)
  - Catalogue, 1915-1916 (Box 198)
  - Catalogue, 1916-1917 (Box 199)
  - Announcement of the Modern Language Group, 1916-1917 (Box 5)
  - Catalogue, 1917-1918 (Box 199)
  - Catalogue, 1918-1919 (Box 199)
  - Catalogue, 1919-1920 (Box 199)
  - Catalogue, 1920-1921 (Box 199)
  - Catalogue, 1921-1922 (Box 199)
  - Catalogue, 1922-1923 (Box 199)
  - Catalogue, 1923-1924 (Box 200)
  - Catalogue, 1924-1925 (Box 200)
  - Catalogue, 1925-1926 (Box 200)
  - Catalogue, 1926-1927 (Box 200)
  - Catalogue, 1927-1928 (Box 200)
  - Catalogue, 1928-1929 (Box 200)
  - An Index of Courses Offered at NYU, 1928-1929 (Box 201)
  - An Index of Courses Offered at NYU, 1929-1930 (Box 201)
  - Catalogue, 1929-1930 (Box 200)
  - Catalogue, 1930-1931 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1931-1932 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1932-1933 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1933-1934 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1934-1935 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1935-1936 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1936-1937 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1937-1938 (Box 189)
  - Catalogue, 1938-1939 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1939-1940 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1940-1941 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1941-1942 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1942-1943 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1944-1945 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1945-1946 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1946-1947 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1947-1948 (Box 190)
  - Catalogue, 1948-1949 (Box 201)
  - Catalogue, 1949-1950 (Box 201)
  - Catalogue, 1950-1951 (Box 201)
  - Catalogue, 1951-1952 (Box 201)
  - General Information, 1955 (Box 201)
  - General Information, 1957 (Box 201)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1964 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1964 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1964 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1965 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1965 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1965 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1966 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1966 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1966 (Box 173)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1967 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1967 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1967 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1968 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1968 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1969 (Box 174)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1969 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1969 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1970 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1970 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 3 (2 copies), 1970 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 4, 1970 (Box 175)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1971 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1971 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin - Part 3, 1971 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin, 1971-1974 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin (2 copies), 1972-1973 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin (School of Education), 1973-1974 (Box 176)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1974 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin - Part 2, 1974 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin, 1975-1976 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin - Part 1, 1976 (Box 177)
  - Bulletin - Part 2 (2 copies), 1976 (Box 177, Box 178)
  - Bulletin, 1977-1978 (Box 178)
  - Registration and Scheduling, November 2015-August 2018
    Website for the registration and scheduling team, which assists with all aspects of class registration, including cross-school registration, dropping and adding classes, class withdrawal, course evaluations, exam schedules, and minor application information.
  - Forms, Policies, and Procedures, August 2016
    Website containing forms and policies for students and administrators, as well as university policies.
  - Forms, Policies and Procedures, September 2016-February 2019
    Forms for students and administrators related to change of student information, Albert SIS and reporting account requests, FERPA, and NYU CIP codes, as well as university policies on FERPA, personal identification numbers, responsible use of NYU computers and data, and other university policies.
  - Registration and Scheduling, September 2016-March 2022
    Website explaining how to register for classes at NYU. Includes information on preparing to register, registering on Albert (NYU's course catalog), cross-school registration, dropping and/or adding classes, class withdrawal, registration schedules, administrative scheduling deadlines, leaves of absence, classroom locations, minor application information, exam schedules, and classroom scheduling. In 2021, the website added tips for successful registration and how to register after disenrollment.
  - School Bulletins, August 2018
    NYU website linking to College of Arts & Science, Arts & Science: Liberal Studies Program, College of Dentistry, Gallatin School of Individualized Study, Graduate School of Arts & Science, Rory Meyers College of Nursing, School of Medicine, School of Professional Studies, Silver School of Social Work, Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development, Stern School of Business - Undergraduate, Stern School of Business - Master of Business Administration, Tandon School of Engineering, Tisch School of the Arts, and Wagner Graduate School of Public Service.
  - Class Search, 2019
    Course search landing page for NYU classes. Includes links to courses by school and department.
  - NYU Online, August 2018-ongoing
    Information on graduate degrees, undergraduate courses, and online certificates available online.
  - New York University Bulletins, January 2024-ongoing
    This webpage includes degree requirements and administrative information about academic programs at New York University across the global campuses. Course numbers are also listed.
- Sunrise Semester (RG 7.3.1.1), 1961-1982
  - Bulletins, 1961-1982 (Box 6)
- Institute of Afro-American Affairs (RG 9.8), 1968-1974
  - Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
- Summer School (RG 16), 1895-2003
  - New York University Announcements of Summer Courses and Bulletins of the Summer School at University Heights, 1895-1898, 1900-1912; cuid18172 (Box 7)
  - New York University Announcement of Summer Courses, 1897; cuid18173 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - New York University Announcement of Summer Courses, 1900; cuid18251 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - New York University Bi-Weekly Bulletin -- Summer School, March 1901; cuid18252 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - New York University Bi-Weekly Bulletin -- University Summer School, March 15, 1902; cuid18253 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - New York University Bi-Weekly Bulletin -- University Summer School, February 15, 1903; cuid18254 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - New York University Bi-Weekly Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, February 15, 1904; cuid18255 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - New York University Summer Courses, circa 1905; cuid18256 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, Revised Announcements, May 12, 1906; cuid18257 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, March 1907; cuid18258 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, April 18, 1908; cuid18259 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights and New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, Revised Announcements, April 3 and 24, 1909; cuid18260 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, Preliminary Announcements and New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, February and April 1910; cuid18261 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, Preliminary Announcements and New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, February and April 1911; cuid18262 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School at University Heights, April 5, 1912; cuid18263 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School, April 10, 1914; cuid18264 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - New York University Bulletin -- The Summer School, April 15, 1915; cuid18265 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Bulletins, 1916-1931 (Box 9)
  - Announcements, flyers, and other ephemera, 1912-1937 (Box 10)
  - New York University Bulletins -- Summer School, 1924-1931; cuid18174 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Summer School - Department of Music Education bulletins, 1925-1934 (Box 178)
  - New York University Bulletins -- Summer School, 1932-1939; cuid18175 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins, 1947-1948, 1952-1956, 1960-1965 (Box 11)
  - Bulletins, 1955-1962 (Volume RG16 Bulletins - Bound 1955-1962 c.1)
  - Bulletins, 1966-1968 (Box 12)
  - Bulletins, 1969-1971 (Box 13)
  - Bulletins, 1971-1973 (Box 14)
  - Bulletins, 1974-1976 (Box 15)
  - Bulletins, 1977-1983 (Box 16)
  - Bulletins, 1984-1988 (Box 17)
  - Bulletins, 1989-1994 (Box 18)
  - Bulletins, 1995-2000 (Box 19)
  - Bulletins, 2001-2003 (Box 20)
  - Summer School - Department of Music Education bulletins, 1925-1934 (Box 178)
- University College of Arts and Science (University Heights) (RG 18), 1893-1973
  - University College Bulletins, 1893-1901; cuid18176 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Bulletins and announcements, 1900-1904, 1914-1943, 1954-1957 (Box 21)
    Includes Havenmeyer Chemical Laboratory courses (1904).
  - University College Bulletins, 1901-1913; cuid18177 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - University College Bulletins, 1913-1925; cuid18178 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1931 (Box 213)
  - Bulletins, 1931-1937 (Box 216)
  - Bulletins, 1932-1940 (Box 216)
  - Bulletins, 1940-1949 (Box 216)
  - Bulletins, 1949-1958 (Box 216)
  - Bulletins, 1957-1973 (Box 22)
- College of Arts and Science (Washington Square) (RG 19), 1903-2016, 2014-ongoing
  Historical Note
  The College offers the B.A. and the B.S. degrees in a wide range of programs in the humanities, science, social sciences, and foreign languages and literatures.
  - Bulletins, 1903-1914 (Box 204)
  - Bulletins, 1911-1941, 1952, 1959-1960 (Box 23)
    Includes Evening Division.
  - Washington Square College Bulletins and Announcements, 1914-1925; cuid18179 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Bulletins, 1925-1935 (Box 211)
  - Bulletins, 1935-1941 (Box 211)
  - Washington Square College Bulletins, 1941-1947; cuid18180 (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square College Bulletins, 1947-1953; cuid18181 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Bulletins, 1953-1960 (Box 213)
  - Bulletins, 1960-1967 (Box 213)
  - Bulletins, 1961-1964, 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Bulletins, 1967-1976 (Box 25)
  - Bulletins, 1976-1981 (Box 26)
  - Bulletins, 1981-1985 (Box 27)
  - Bulletins, 1986-1990 (Box 28)
  - Bulletins, 1991-1996 (Box 29)
  - Bulletins, 1996-2000 (Box 30)
  - Bulletins, 2000-2008 (Box 31)
  - Bulletins, 2008-2012 (Box 32)
  - Bulletins, 2012-2016 (Box 33)
  - Bulletins (PDFs), 2000-2016
  - College of Arts and Science Bulletin, April 2014-August 2018
    Landing page for the CAS bulletin that includes policies, requirements, course offerings, schedules, activities, tuition, fees, and calendar of the school and its departments and programs. PDFs linked include bulletins for 2012-2014, 2014-2016, 2016-2018, and 2018-2020.
  - College of Arts and Science Bulletin, May 2014-September 2016
  - College of Arts and Science Bulletin, November 2017-ongoing